(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
(The new commercial zone for Round 3, amusement park)
(Team up and sell 100 bowls.)
(Lee Sung Hoon and Go Seok Hyun)
(Kim Kwan Hoon and Kim Ho Yoon)
(Lee Yeon Bok and Kim Min Seong)
(Jung Ho Young and Hong Seok Cheon)
(Kim Mi Ryeong and Edward Kwon)
(Choi Sang Hyun and Kim Hoon)
This round will be a blind competition.
(A blind team mission)
(They can attract customers when wearing mascot costumes.)
Each alliance team must...
choose 2 out of 4 available dishes.
(100 serving relay team match)
The two selected dishes will be sold in a relay format.
(Dish for the 1st half, dish for the 2nd half)
The starting team must...
sell 50 bowls before...
the following team can begin selling.
Including 50 bowls of the following team,
the 1st 2 restaurants to sell a total of 100 bowls will...
advance to the next round.
(Only the 1st 2 alliance teams to sell 100 dishes will survive.)
(Including a beverage, each dish is sold for 13 dollars.)
However...
Is it not ready yet?
(If a customer complaint occurs)
One additional dish as a penalty.
(For 2 points of customer ratings,)
(1 additional dish is added.)
(For 1 point of customer ratings,)
(2 additional dishes are added.)
(They must sell all penalty bowls to survive.)
(100 serving relay team match starts.)
(Kim Mi Ryeong and Edward Kwon's Aunties Kitchen)
We're the starting team.
(Kim Mi Ryeong in charge of the first half menu)
It has a variety of flavours,
so I thought the customers would like it.
We have five orders.
We just got a new one, so we have six.
Okay.
(Corn cheese)
The cheese got too hard.
Hold on. Let's see.
This is too thick.
We were short on time...
and had to prepare a large quantity,
so we made a lot of the corn cheese in advance.
But the cheese completely hardened.
Wait a minute.
(Glancing cautiously)
Seok Su, get the wok on the stove.
(Getting the wok ready)
Pour two cartons of heavy cream for me.
Okay.
We're on the same team.
As a senior in the industry,
the right thing to do was to step in and help them out.
We're going to reduce it.
When making cream pasta, you reduce the cream.
I had to reduce it and get the right consistency.
- The cheese must be melted.
- Okay.
I was incredibly grateful,
but I felt bad about it.
It was our dish,
yet they were fixing it for us.
(Jun Seong is frozen with guilt over his mistake.)
- We have another order.
- Okay.
We have another one.
(Orders are piling up with nothing going out.)
Gosh, the cheese isn't melting.
(The cheese shows no signs of melting.)
Let me see. Lift it.
No, it's a mess. There's no way to fix it.
Let's put a bowl...
or something underneath it and strain it.
(Preparing the strainer)
Move out of the way.
I figured it was best to keep...
the sauce that had absorbed the corn flavour...
and quickly remove clumps of cheese.
Is it okay now?
We reheated the sauce mixed with the heavy cream.
Do we have more corn?
- Yes, we have canned corn.
- Can you add one can?
Then we added more corn...
to increase the quantity.
It was essentially a creamy corn sauce.
About this much?
(Adding more salt for seasoning)
I have some cheese over there.
I'll give you this cheese.
- Sprinkle some on top.
- Okay.
- Okay, you got it now?
- Yes.
At the temperature the dish will be served,
the cheese should be warm enough to melt...
when mixed in.
So we decided to add the cheese at the end.
- You understand it now, right?
- Yes.
Okay, let's go.
Let's do this.
Do we plate it like that?
(Spreading the sweet potato mousse...)
(and topping it with corn cheese)
(Sprinkling the cheese on top before serving)
Currently, we have 13 orders.
- Okay.
- Thirteen orders?
Yes, we have 13 orders.
Clear this area...
- and prepare 13 dishes here.
- Okay.
We'll send them out all in one go.
I don't know if I could call it taking the lead,
but I felt that...
establishing a system quickly was important.
Clear this area first.
Is that corn?
- Yes.
- Put the corn here.
I'll cut the gimbap here.
Yes, just keep cutting them.
I'll put the salad with the sauce and serve it.
He told us what needed to be done first.
Thanks to him, we were off to a smooth start.
He was amazing.
As expected, he knew what he was doing.
For a team that hasn't worked together to find its rhythm,
someone has to step up...
- And lead the way.
- and lead the way.
Edward did it...
very well.
So everything came together more smoothly.
Is it done? This one is ready.
(Food being plated quickly)
Enjoy your food.
- Most of our orders are out.
- Okay.
(Number of orders after 20 minutes)
(3rd place: Kim Mi Ryeong and Edward Kwon, 19 dishes)
Look at the sign.
Isn't Chap Chap Chu popular?
It is.
(Chap Chu, Chap Chu, Chap Chap Chu)
(Crazy Flavour Restaurant)
- It's Chap Chap Chu.
- Chap Chap Chu.
Customer ratings are important.
We fought hard to make it back here. We can't lose.
Our two teams have been...
strong candidates for elimination...
in every mission so far.
Naturally, no one sees us as a threat.
(During the restaurant ledger inspections)
(Starting with Kids Restaurant,)
(other restaurants were being inspected.)
Is there no one?
(Crazy Flavour Restaurant)
Why isn't anyone checking us?
I thought,
"They don't care what we do."
Dying once is hard enough. What's hard about dying twice?
We wanted to show them how immortal we were.
We'll keep surviving.
(Surviving team from revival match, Kim Kwan Hoon and Kim Ho Yoon)
Feel free to tell us your ideas.
- Our restaurant name...
- Our name...
When it comes to naming something,
it's easier when one person makes...
a suggestion and everyone else agrees.
We'll think about it.
We'll think of something catchy.
After a lot of intense thinking,
we decided on a Gen Z concept...
aimed at middle and high school students.
We named it Crazy Flavour Restaurant.
"Chap Chap Chu" is a trendy and catchy expression...
for describing something delicious.
It was a funny and witty concept...
that we could use for the restaurant's sign and promotion.
(Crazy Flavour Restaurant)
Hello, puppy.
(Hello, it's this way.)
I was born...
in 1979, and I turned 48 this year.
It was my first time wearing a mascot costume.
I can't see anything.
The eyes are too far away.
The eyes were over here like this.
I could barely see anything.
Gosh, I stepped on a camera.
(A dog with a limited field of vision)
I'm stepping on all the cameras.
(Greeting customers with a narrow field of view)
(He drops his glove.)
Please help me find my glove.
(A customer helps him.)
(The mascot costume promotion is hard for the 48-year-old.)
Thank you.
I took on that role, so I wanted to give it a shot.
Trying something new can be fun.
There's no reason I can't make it work.
Do we have the sample?
Here's the sample.
We were the first team to start.
The most important was choosing an item...
that was perfectly suited to the location.
- This could work really well.
- Right.
I'm all for it.
If we choose this, we could make the perfect dish for it.
- Exactly.
- Shall we go with this?
- Okay.
- Yes, we made our decision.
I didn't think there would be another team...
that uses the container better than we could.
For the first round, our menu items are...
bouquet fritter and honey garlic fried rice cake.
(They're making tteokbokki again.)
Our strategy is to make a milder...
honey garlic sauce with plenty of condensed milk.
It's a type of rice cake that anyone can...
easily enjoy.
As more of a side dish than a full meal,
it can be enjoyed as an appetizer.
We deliberately chose this menu item.
It will be very delicious.
(Sweet and crunchy honey garlic fried rice cake)
The key to our fritter dish is...
putting everything on skewers and arranging it like a bouquet.
(Chicken, shrimp, squid)
(Honey garlic fried rice cake)
(Gochujang aioli)
The drink sits at the bottom of the container.
The food spreads upward and gives it a lot of height.
When someone is carrying it with one hand or both,
people would see it and think, "Which restaurant is it from?"
We thought the visual appeal would draw people to us.
Gosh, let's get that. Snowflake chicken thigh.
- That looks good.
- Which one?
It looks like deep-fried shrimp.
It's unusual.
- Shall we get it?
- Okay.
(Customers gather after seeing the sample.)
- We have one order.
- Okay.
(Snowflake cheese)
When it goes out, people will be...
impressed by it and buy it.
(Hoping the customers themselves would promote it)
(One person interested)
(Another one interested)
That bouquet fritter looks good.
After looking at it,
the fritter skewers look delicious.
Make an order.
(Thanks to the visual appeal, the waiting line gets long.)
Shall we get one for now?
I can't wait to try it.
The orders are coming in like crazy.
They'll keep coming.
Are you frying chicken right now?
Yes, I'm frying chicken.
We still need ten more dishes.
Ten? My gosh.
A lot of orders came in all of a sudden.
This is good.
(Crazy Flavour Restaurant is advancing quickly.)
Here's your order.
Do I press call for all the incoming orders?
Yes.
I expect it to be a race against the clock.
Who can sell the most the fastest.
How many orders did we get? What number is it?
We're at number 43.
(Crazy Flavour Restaurant sold 7 dishes.)
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- The number is 7324.
- Yes, please take it.
(Crazy Flavour Restaurant sold 8 dishes.)
We have to fry them according to the numbers.
There's enough chicken.
Shrimp.
There's shrimp too.
We have no squid rings right now.
Can you fry four squid rings?
Really? They run out fast.
We had three different items. And as we were making a lot,
it was taking longer than expected.
Is this all...
- the deep-fried shrimp?
- I'll fry more right away.
- Please keep frying them.
- Okay.
(1 of the 3 items keeps running short.)
Pay immediately? One?
- Yes.
- Would you like to pay?
Can you make one more?
Please wait for a minute.
It'll take two minutes.
You can take your time,
- but please fry them as a full set.
- Okay.
We're just frying it now, so please wait.
- We'll make it very delicious.
The frying was taking...
longer than I thought.
I started to get anxious.
Can I fry with him?
- Go ahead.
- It's okay.
- We need 14 sets.
- Take the chicken.
Take the chicken.
We're not fast enough. Can you fry next to him?
They get mixed?
Otherwise, we wouldn't get the quality we want.
- This is fast enough.
- Okay.
We're working fast enough.
If I don't do it my way...
I can't trust...
when someone else makes fritters.
I notice little things that don't look right.
(The line of waiting customers is getting longer.)
Enjoy your food.
Please pick up your order.
- I'll serve the 2 right away.
- Okay, 2.
We can do this.
It's a race against time, so we need to get the orders out fast.
We had our orders piled up.
Could you speed up the frying a little?
I'll help him with frying from now on.
It has to be coated with batter.
I'll take care of it.
Like that?
(Putting fritters in the wok as well)
(Making the fritter coating with a spatula)
I really didn't want to get eliminated.
You should put the chicken on the skewers instead.
- I haven't put all of it yet.
- The orders need to go out now.
The fritters are over there.
- We need to send out 16 sets.
- I know.
I was very flustered.
As he had already started helping me,
I didn't think there was anything I could do.
Can we keep going?
- We can send out five more dishes.
- Okay.
Hello, please take your order.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Hello.
(Crazy Flavour Restaurant catches up on orders.)
What's your number?
Dip it in gochujang aioli.
Okay.
Only two teams survive,
- so I'm feeling impatient.
- Yes.
(Unaware of the kitchen's situation, the puppy is attracting customers.)
I'm very sorry you have to see a middle-aged man like me...
do all the stunts.
Since 3 to 4 days ago,
I learned every single dance I could do with a mask on.
(Dance 1)
(Dance 2)
(Surprised)
(Thank you for ordering.)
Because we ordered this.
Just for this...
(I can't see right now.)
He's so cute.
Seriously.
That...
(Bouquet fritters and honey garlic fried rice cakes)
- Eat first.
- Gosh.
Try the rice cake. It's good.
- Is the rice cake good?
- It's good.
(Crispy)
That sound.
I like the rice cake.
- Is the rice cake good?
- Yes.
Deep-fried squid is amazing. It's so good.
The rice cake tastes like garlic bread.
- The fritter.
- It's delicious.
The batter is fantastic.
(Amazed)
I've never had such a fritter before.
The rice cake is so chewy and nice.
This is amazing.
This is tasty too.
Deep-fried squid tastes great.
I'll take a short break.
- Drink water.
- I was the most popular one.
I can imagine.
Thanks for your hard work.
This is no joke.
A two-star customer rating has occurred.
- A plate is added...
- What?
to Crazy Flavour Restaurant as a penalty.
- Why?
- I don't know.
(1 more plate added to sell)
Why...
Why did we get a penalty?
What is it?
What was the problem?
It felt as if someone hit me.
(The next announcement continues.)
- To Crazy Flavour Restaurant.
- Again?
A two-star customer rating...
- has occurred.
- What is it?
A plate is added as a penalty.
Why?
As long as it's not me.
Chef Ho Yoon, how many penalty plates did we get?
Two.
- Two in total?
- Yes.
Why?
I don't know. We need to find out the reason.
I was very flustered.
"What's the reason?"
Is anything tough to chew?
It can't be the fritters.
We need to find out why.
What could it be?
Maybe because it's hard to pull it out of a skewer.
It grabs onto the skewer when it gets cooked.
Shrimps and squids grab onto the skewer.
When they pulled it out of the skewer,
maybe it didn't pull out smoothly and broke.
Could that be why?
I thought it was my dish's problem.
Skewers are hard to eat.
Why is it so hard to eat?
(Annoyed)
This is pissing me off.
I hope they'll serve it without the skewer.
Me too.
It's so hard to eat.
Normally,
we twist it a bit before serving.
Or it just crumbles.
You need to be careful. One by one.
It's easy to eat that way.
If the problem is with my dish, I need to fix it quickly.
So I taught people how to do it inside my dog costume.
- Can I have this?
- Yes. You can eat it.
What?
Pull it out?
Twist it and pull it out?
- Okay.
- No wonder it won't come off.
- Twist it?
- Twist it? Okay.
This is...
- We can't have any more penalties.
- My number is 0525.
Please give me a moment. It'll be served soon.
(Number of orders after 20 minutes)
(4th place, Kim Kwan Hoon and Kim Ho Yoon, 18 plates)
Judging from all the menus,
today won't be an easy fight.
(Wandering Panda)
The panda is the protagonist.
We have the cutest signboard.
- Did you see the panda outside?
- Yes, I did.
It's cute, right?
(Lee Yeon Bok and Kim Min Seong)
Can't we use Fu Bao?
- Fu Bao?
- And name it "Wandering Fu Bao."
(Name the restaurant "Wandering Panda.")
Even Fu Bao who ran away wants to eat it.
She returned to eat this.
I think it's a good idea.
- Wandering Fu Bao.
- That's fun.
- Wandering Panda.
(Lee Yeon Bok and Kim Min Seong, Wandering Panda)
- This is our plate, right?
- Yes, we'll use this.
(Yeon Bok chooses half and half bowl.)
Stir-fried noodles, tangsuyuk, and bao.
- So three menus?
- Yes.
- Three?
- We'll stir-fry noodles...
Can we just do bao and tangsuyuk?
We can't do that.
If we fill up the plate generously,
people won't be able to resist it.
They won't be able to resist it.
I'm confident I can sell it quickly and call it a day.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Eyes blazing)
Team Wandering Panda prepared...
Panda's Tasty Three-menu Set.
It looks very full.
(3 filling menus)
Stir-fried noodles to replace a meal.
(Menu 1: Shrimp and ham stir-fried noodles)
Ham goes on top of it.
Kids love ham.
They'll definitely beg their parents to buy it.
And then, there's tangsuyuk.
Kids will be tempted by tangsuyuk.
I planned it all.
(Menu 2: Special tangsuyuk)
The last one is jjajang bulgogi bao.
It's bulgogi with jjajang flavour.
You can't find this easily.
(Jjajang-flavoured bulgogi is added to a bun.)
I put in a lot of effort into jjajang bulgogi bao.
Both adults and kids can have it.
(Panda's Tasty 3-menu Set, 13 dollars)
(Shrimp and ham stir-fried noodles, special tangsuyuk,)
(jjajang bulgogi bao)
- Are these 50 plates?
- Yes.
Fifty.
We'll be done in 50 minutes.
One plate per minute?
(To bring out fast orders)
(Laughing)
(Here comes a panda.)
This...
You must be so hot.
The panda is dancing too!
Panda.
- Panda.
- The panda is saying hi.
Panda. You're so cute.
Hello.
- My gosh.
- I cheered you on just now.
- I cheered you on.
- Panda.
Panda.
Hey.
- Panda and Squid are fighting.
- Who are you?
Go, Panda!
- Go, Panda!
Are the orders coming in?
- They're ordering now.
- From us?
- Yes.
- They ordered.
(Orders)
The orders...
They came in.
- How many?
- One. No, it's two.
Two.
Okay, this much first.
(Double frying tangsuyuk)
(He prepares jjajang bulgogi bao right away.)
(Ordering)
- Five.
- Five?
Six, seven.
Eight.
I didn't prepare that much.
We need to deep-fry more tangsuyuk.
- How many did we serve?
- Goodness.
I'm not checking the bills.
(It's impossible to check the bills.)
- Just keep serving.
- Yes.
Keep it going. I'll press the buttons.
Don't mind it here.
I'll call them as soon as the dishes are out.
(Kim Min Seong in charge of the cash register)
As they say, experience shows.
I can see what should be done in what situation.
Chef Yeon Bok is going to be swarmed with cooking.
Since it's a team mission,
I'm trying my best not to get in anyone's way.
- Did you put the hams?
- Yes, three pieces.
Three pieces.
(Wandering Panda sold 4 plates.)
(Wandering Panda sold 5 plates.)
(Wandering Panda sold 6 plates.)
(Wandering Panda sold 7 plates.)
(As Min Seong manages the register, things go smoothly.)
(Attracting customers)
I'll stir-fry it right away.
I'll make a lot.
Let's go, a whole batch.
After a while, we got used to each other...
and started to work well together.
And we got faster.
Let's go.
Let's go for 50.
A plate is added to Crazy Flavour Restaurant...
as a penalty.
(A plate is added to Crazy Flavour Restaurant...)
(as a penalty.)
Three plates are added as a penalty.
My goodness.
(3 plates are added as a penalty.)
(They suddenly hear the news about the other teams' penalties.)
One plate is added as a penalty each.
- Who? Us?
- No.
Not us.
(Starting to get worried)
"We can't only aim to sell many."
"The customer ratings are very important," was what I thought.
Add a lot.
- Is this cold?
- Sorry?
Are the baos are not steamed?
- They're steamed.
- Goodness.
No.
You can't take them out in advance.
I understand.
They need to be re-steamed. They've gone cold.
Take them out from the steamer before you serve them.
(Take the warm ones out.)
I'll do it.
(Glancing)
You can't pour the sauce yet.
Pour it right before you serve it.
(The sauce has already been poured.)
It'll become stale.
(Yeon Bok is worried about getting a penalty.)
If we can't serve our dish quickly,
Min's can't even open their stall.
"We'll sell out quickly and get Min's to open."
That was all I could think about.
Push it a bit to this side...
and fit the bao inside. A bit more.
(Lee Yeon Bok takes immense care into the quality.)
The Chinese cuisine is popular.
Everyone suddenly started ordering from them.
Maybe because kids can enjoy it too.
There's tangsuyuk too, Ye Jin.
Tangsuyuk.
(Eating)
Dad will eat tangsuyuk too.
(Lee Yeon Bok's dish is convenient for a family to share.)
(Surprised)
(Humming)
It's crispy outside and moist inside.
Ham!
(Stir-fried noodles)
Good?
Do you like it?
(Nodding)
(Jjajang bulgogi bao)
That's it.
How is it?
Doesn't it taste better?
(Nodding)
(One more bite)
Eat it all the way.
You can do it.
Their tangsuyuk is really good.
- Is it good?
- Yes.
It's so delicious.
It's so good.
- Five stars.
- It's so soft.
And tangsuyuk isn't hard.
- I rate it five stars.
- Me too.
- Definitely five stars.
- This.
It's so good.
(The tangsuyuk sauce is sweet and salty and nice.)
(With the kids' total support, they have 0 penalty.)
(Number of orders after 20 minutes)
(4th place, Lee Yeon Bok and Kim Min Seong, 17 plates)
The stall which most people...
- are ordering from...
- What is it?
Go over there.
- Lulu Land.
What is Lulu Land?
Currently, Lulu Land has...
twenty-five plates ordered.
(Lulu Land, 25 plates)
(1st place, Lee Sung Hoon and Go Seok Hyun, 25 plates)
Lulu is a squirrel.
Lulu, where are you?
Hello, thank you for coming all the way here.
Hello.
(Lulu appears.)
You look much cooler in your casual clothes.
So do you.
(Lulu Land, Lee Sung Hoon and Go Seok Hyun)
Have you thought of a stall name?
We could go with something "Express."
You startled me.
I was thinking of "Express" too,
and you brought it up first.
That's nice.
We could add "One Day..."
and go with "One Day Express."
Or something really cute.
I have a very cute personality.
So we can make it cute,
and I'll attract the customers in a cute manner as well.
(Stumped)
If you want to make it cute, rather than One Day Express,
- Lulu Express sounds cuter.
- I love it.
- "Lulu." Like this.
- Lulu sounds cute.
(Lulu Express sounds cuter.)
Our strategy is cuteness.
Being cute solves everything.
Delicious and cute.
Cuteness wins.
We wanted it to be like us.
We poured our everything into making it cute.
We mixed the characteristics of each teammate.
Lulu is a squirrel,
and it has a chubby face.
I tried to portray myself.
But it's in very good shape.
(Go Seok Hyun's face and Lee Sung Hoon's broad back)
It's not just a fat one.
Lulu Land aimed to be a cute brand.
The first menu prepared by Koony is...
DonDon Set.
(DonDon Set)
It's my signature brand,
and I was able to...
get myself out there with it.
It was a tendon brand.
(Tendon made Lee Sung Hoon a legend in Yeonnam-dong.)
(6am, menu introduction time)
Tendon.
He's the master of tendon.
- That's a really good set.
- It really is.
They're very formidable.
That for 13 dollars?
This one is quite strong.
I think Lulu Land is a strong opponent.
People even say one can never lose with tendon.
It's that popular of a dish.
Kids really like udon.
Tendon...
and cold bibim udon.
So it's DonDon Set.
(The first half menu: Assorted tendon and cold bibim udon)
- We are!
- One!
As long as we don't make mistakes,
people will queue up for sure.
(The queue is incredibly long.)
Tendon looks good.
- But...
- This looks so good.
- Which one?
- Bibim udon.
I do want to try it.
- It's cold bibim udon.
- Right.
Tendon and bibim udon look really good.
Bibim udon.
(The queue is a lot longer than the other stalls.)
(The influx of customers doesn't stop.)
We got six in total.
- Got it.
- Okay.
Cut various ingredients...
and apply the batter.
(Adding one round of sesame oil to enhance the flavour)
The fritters for tendon are tempura.
We drop the batter from a higher place...
to check if it blooms like a flower when the oil hits an ingredient.
(The fundamental, deep-fried shrimps)
(His signature deep-fried poached eggs)
(Deep-fried fatsia shoots)
(And deep-fried conger eels)
(Legendary tendon is deep-fried as soon as the order comes in.)
Good. People are highly satisfied.
Thank you. Enjoy.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
(Lulu Land sells 26 plates.)
(Lulu Land sells 27 plates.)
Thank you.
- Thank you. Enjoy.
- Thank you.
(Lulu Land sells 28 plates.)
(Lee Sung Hoon and Go Seok Hyun)
We must have a team dinner after we win.
You bet.
I really hope we'll stay close until the end.
I hope we win.
We can do it.
- We can do it.
We are!
- One!
(The cute young adults build their teamwork.)
(Assorted tendon by Lee Sung Hoon)
It's so hot.
Gosh, it's hot.
They must be deep-frying them on the spot.
They're really warm.
Conger eel.
(This is fatsia shoots.)
This is the best.
They're really focusing...
- on the quality.
- I agree.
- It's freshly deep-fried.
- If they were cold...
If they'd gone stale...
(The fritters are crispy because they're freshly deep-fried.)
(Cold bibim udon by Lee Sung Hoon)
This is so good.
The sauce looks cheesy, but it isn't.
It's not cheesy at all.
- It's salty and nice.
- It's savoury.
Yes. It washes down...
the greasy taste of the fritters.
(They complement each other as they are served in half and half.)
Lulu Land's fritters are cooked...
by someone exceptional.
I'm sure it was cooked by a Japanese cuisine head chef...
in a hotel.
Even with the batter,
the egg remained soft-boiled instead of getting fully cooked.
- It was about to flow over.
- Yes.
(With overwhelming praises, Lulu Land is full of customers.)
A street restaurant has achieved...
fifty orders.
- Already?
- That was fast.
That's fast.
Lulu Land...
has achieved 50 orders.
We did it.
Focus until the final plate.
It was my first time winning a match on a survival show.
I was really happy.
I was elated,
and all we had to do was serve all the orders.
Don't get too excited.
Seok Hyun, it'll be fine as long as you do your job well.
- Tae Hee.
- Yes?
Don't forget what roles we're supposed to play.
We could finish the first half...
faster than the other teams.
But...
until the last plate is served to the customer,
you cannot open the second plate.
(Current orders received: 50 plates)
(Lulu Land has currently served 33 plates.)
How many plates do we have left?
- Seventeen.
- Seventeen plates.
- We have 17 plates left.
- Okay.
(If they serve the 17 plates,)
(they can unlock the second plates.)
We're done once we serve all these, right?
- Okay.
- That's perfect.
Here come the eels.
(Lee Sung Hoon deep-fries each and every one with care.)
This is bad.
Is Lulu Land the stall we've talked about?
Yes.
Can we catch up?
I only have 25 cotton candies.
- So it's...
- Twenty-five?
They fell.
(Remaining cotton candies: 21)
We won't have enough cotton candies.
(Stuck with making cotton candies)
Seok Cheon needs to go all out.
He must be so frustrated.
He's so talkative, but he's not allowed to talk.
Cotton candy is free, Seon Wu!
Cotton candy.
"Feed our children Korean beef."
"Tasty and healthy."
- Do I order here?
- Yes.
It's cotton candy.
It's been a while since I've had one.
I've last had it...
when I was young.
We got an order. Okay.
- I'll cook two at once.
- Two.
I'll add five.
Okay.
Western-style French fries.
BBQ that's made in the style of Chinese cuisine.
Cheese sauce that children love.
And salsa that'll balance out...
the richness on top.
With that, a yuzu soda.
(Setting up in a soda pop container)
Hurry up!
Okay.
"Hurry up?"
Hurry. Give me a minute.
(Charcoal-grilled Korean rib-eye skewer)
One of each, okay? One left, one right.
Very nice.
(Korean rib-eye party cup grilled by the chef, 13 dollars)
Hello. Cotton candy, please.
Thank you.
(Chef Land: Sold 31 orders)
(Chef Land: Sold 32 orders)
Thank you. Enjoy.
It may fall down.
- Please carry it separately.
- Okay.
(Chef Land is on a roll.)
Are you okay, Ho Young?
Yes, I'm fine.
The problem is whether we can move on to the next menu.
Exactly.
- Thank you. Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- A plate...
is added to Chef Land as a penalty.
How come?
What went wrong?
This is nerve-racking.
We must serve faster.
Is that so?
We can make it if we serve the moment the order comes in.
- Okay.
- Got it.
A plate...
is added to Chef Land as a penalty.
(Chef Land: Sold 33 orders)
(Chef Land: Sold 32 orders)
A plate...
is added to Chef Land as a penalty.
- What's wrong with us?
- We are getting a lot of penalties.
(They keep getting penalties.)
I'm going to drink a soda.
(Agitated)
(Grilled Korean beef skewer by Jung Ho Young)
When I had the first bite of the beef,
it was quite tough.
I agree.
I like the smokiness.
Me too, but it's too tough.
It's tough.
The meat is tough.
(Even the customers who liked it)
- It's good.
- Is it?
But the center is tough.
The meat itself is good.
(It's tough and thick, while the thin parts are overcooked.)
(The meat is as tender as cotton candy.)
(It's quite tough but delicious.)
(The skewer is really tough.)
(The thick meat is tender and well-seasoned.)
(Opinions on Chef Land's first-half menu are sharply divided.)
The penalty.
- It's here.
- Right.
The beef wasn't super tender.
The Korean beef wasn't juicy...
and savoury...
like you'd expect.
The meat being beef was a real...
- attention grabber.
- Yes.
But was the taste....
not what the customers expected?
(During prepping)
The meat has to be prepped well. If it turns out to be tough,
- we'll get penalized.
- For sure.
If the Korean beef doesn't turn out the way...
customers expect it to, it may have the opposite effect.
The riskiest is Chef Land.
Customers might...
They'll expect it to melt in their mouths.
Exactly.
As the meat was prepped in bulk,
not all the pieces were tenderized.
There was inconsistency.
(The large-batch resulted in some inconsistency.)
Can I try a piece?
The meat.
The fatty pieces are fine.
(The meat has an inconsistent texture.)
Three plates...
are added to Chef Land as a penalty.
Three?
A plate...
is added to Chef Land as a penalty.
I'm losing it.
I took the containers out.
As it kept increasing,
it just...
(Servings left: 16)
(Servings left: 17)
(Servings left: 7)
(Servings left: 10)
(Servings left: 6)
(Servings left: 7)
It's a relay.
We were the ones who had to pass on the key.
But it didn't go as planned.
We weren't in a situation where we could change the ingredient.
Let's serve the cooked warm meat right away.
(Decided to serve as quickly as possible)
(Another restaurant is also slicing steak.)
(Steak cream pasta)
(The whole family is enjoying the steak together.)
This must be kid-friendly.
I'll take this piece.
- You sure are digging in.
- It's good.
- Should we get another one?
- Look at you dig in.
(Kids Restaurant)
With many young customers in mind,
we used drawings...
to make children our main target.
(Literally kids restaurant)
(Kids Restaurant)
The dishes are only made...
with ingredients that children can eat.
(A clean dish that children will like)
We prepared jambon cream pasta with steak.
(A family with a child)
This one here.
I'm sure Ha Yul will eat it.
- Which one?
- Right?
Yes, it's cream pasta.
There are also tangsuyuk and meat.
It looks good.
- Kids Restaurant?
- Kids Restaurant, Sun Woo?
It has your favourite...
meat and pasta.
- I'm excited.
- Me too.
(A menu clearly aimed at children)
I must have a taste of this one.
- I'm a huge fan of pasta.
- They are filming only us.
I'm digging in.
Go ahead.
I'm trying this one.
Hey.
Try this, guys.
The cream is...
It's creamy to the point that even babies can eat it.
There are chefs over there.
Help me. Your order is up.
Where do I put this?
- Oh, my.
- Where was this?
- Here, right?
- The bear...
The steak isn't tough at all.
Unbelievable.
This is the happiest lunch I've ever had.
It's even better than lunch at school.
- Exactly.
- Right?
- Seung Jae.
- Yes?
We have 13 orders.
I'll just keep cooking regardless.
- Yes, keep going.
- Okay.
A lot more customers ordered than expected.
We really felt the need...
to serve quickly.
Eleven orders, Seung Jae.
Eleven?
It's been 20 minutes since they ordered.
We had three stoves in total.
As we cooked right after we got the order,
there was a delay in cooking time.
(The dish takes longer than expected.)
Seung Jae, use a bigger pan and cook two servings at once.
We're backed up too much.
- I know how you feel.
- The pan... Right.
(Using a bigger pan)
(Switching all pans)
(From cooking 3 orders at a time...)
(to 6 orders at a time)
I'll cook two orders at a time.
- How many in total?
- Six.
Six?
Unbelievable.
(As they change the pans, they make it faster to cook.)
Six in one go?
Yes.
(As they change the pans, they make it faster to cook.)
The orders came in quickly.
If we do well, the results may be good.
- Here are two.
- Okay.
- We'll keep serving.
(The orders are picking up speed.)
- I'll handle that first.
- Number 9059?
(Cooking and waiting)
I'll get it out as quickly as possible.
One of the street restaurants...
has sold 50 plates.
(Current time)
(A restaurant has sold 50 plates.)
(Which team sold 50 plates 1st?)
The first restaurant to sell out 50 plates is...
Wandering Panda.
You may open the second box.
(1st place of the 1st half)
As expected.
Serve this, and we're done.
The last order has been served.
We're done.
(Lee Yeon Bok reached the halfway point in 1st place.)
As expected.
Lee Yeon Bok!
We must catch up to Lee Yeon Bok.
- Oh, dear.
- My gosh.
You heard that, right? We need to serve fast.
What a big twist.
(The secret to coming in 1st place in the 1st half is...)
Are those new orders?
Yes, 3, 4, 5.
(Even when the orders come pouring in,)
(he sends out the plates with an overwhelming cooking speed.)
(Cooking fiercely)
(Lee Yeon Bok and Kim Min Seong)
(Alone with a wok)
(He cooks 5 portions in an average of 3 minutes.)
You may take it.
The customer who was notified and came first, take it.
Is it already done?
This one is Mom's.
Our Panda order is up.
Already?
The food needs to be served fast!
Food can't be served slowly, Seung Jae.
We have to serve fast, but our speed is...
(Unlike the other teams racing against time)
This is bad.
Have all the orders been served?
We're done.
Okay.
(He's not just fast.)
It's old-fashioned tangsuyuk with a bit of glutinous rice.
It's good.
- Tangsuyuk is delicious.
- Right?
The chef has to cook fine-dining food.
Otherwise, it's impossible to make a dish like this.
The meat between the buns is seasoned evenly throughout.
Our team was faster than the other teams.
Coming in first place is always great, no?
It's the best feeling in the world.
"Yes, we did it!" That's what it feels like.
This is where it starts. We've got to sell faster.
It's completely over only after we sell 100 orders.
- Next one.
We did our share!
Give it your all,
and we'll reach first place!
Wandering Panda.
Open the second box.
(Wandering Panda, 1st chef: Lee Yeon Bok)
(Sold out)
(2nd chef: Kim Min Seong)
(Wandering Panda)
How's the pace? Is it fast?
The prepping is done. We just need to fill it up.
(What is confident Kim Min Seong's second half menu?)
We actually went...
to an amusement park last week.
- You did?
- Yes.
From what I experienced and saw,
everyone had...
churros and hot dogs.
So we were thinking of a dessert...
or snack menu.
After Yeon Bok serves lunch first...
(If the first half was a meal,)
(the second half which is slightly after lunchtime...)
We thought dessert was a good idea.
Some may not have had a meal yet.
Some may have arrived late.
We prepared a sandwich as a meal.
A big croissant sandwich...
and croffle on the side.
Serving a meal and a dessert.
(A combination of dessert and a simple meal)
As for the sandwich...
Tomato, romaine, cheese,
and the filling is made with rose cream chicken.
(On to the croffle made with croissant dough)
Sprinkling some Oreo crumbles on top.
Topping it off with some vanilla ice cream.
Making ears with Oreos.
(Chicken sandwich and ice cream croffle by Kim Min Seong)
Put ice cream here.
(Ready to serve the food)
It's my turn now.
(The second half panda of Wandering Panda...)
(is Lee Yeon Bok.)
There's even a panda.
A panda is over there.
- The panda has changed.
- Right?
The panda suddenly has rough male hands.
You're right.
I wonder who the one inside the panda outfit is.
It'd be funny when they watch the show.
(A panda munching on grass)
It'd be funny when people find out the panda is Chef Lee.
The panda looking after our children is great.
I don't want to leave.
- What's the panda doing over there?
- Right?
It seems the menu has changed.
What?
Rose cream chicken sandwich...
and panda ice cream.
Panda ice cream croffle?
I need snacks.
I already had a meal earlier.
I'm craving dessert right now.
Is that so?
We must be getting both.
Would you like to place the order?
(Order)
Here it comes.
The order is coming in.
Our ingredients have been fully prepped.
All we need to do is fill them up and serve.
It's done once the ice cream is on top, right?
Yes, place the ice cream, sprinkle the crumbles, and done.
(Served as soon as ordered)
Take your order. Please take your order.
It comes with the croffle.
(Realising)
(The orders keep coming in.)
Another order.
Four.
Please take your order.
Take your order.
(Lee Yeon Bok and Kim Min Seong)
- Okay.
- The team currently in the lead...
is Wandering Panda.
Nice.
You scared me.
Byeong Ho!
"We did it! Keep it up, guys!"
That was what crossed my head.
(Lee Yeon Bok and Kim Min Seong in the lead)
(Sold 57 orders)
It's all about speed from now on.
Let's go.
(The restaurants grew impatient because of Yeon Bok's lead.)
A second street restaurant...
has sold 50 plates.
We're almost there.
We're close.
What?
Enjoy.
Are we done?
The second restaurant to sell out 50 plates is...
Crazy Flavour Restaurant.
- Enjoy.
- Sold out 50 orders.
(The last customer of first half has picked up her order.)
Good. Enjoy.
- The second menu.
- Open...
the second box.
Okay.
Yes, the second menu.
Cook as soon as the order comes in.
Okay.
Things went according to plan.
I felt this thrill that...
we could possibly win.
(1st to sell out 50 orders)
(2nd to sell out 50 orders)
(Meanwhile, Aunties Kitchen)
(Hot)
(Sold 44 orders)
That's not important right now.
(The reason Aunties Kitchen is in a rush)
(Outside the restaurant is now quiet.)
People go where the mascot costumes are.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Should I go outside?
We have no orders right now.
- Let's step outside for a minute.
- No orders?
No.
(The new mascot arrives,)
(and kids come flocking.)
How nice.
(Interested)
Hi.
Is it actually good?
(Nodding)
I'll make sure to enjoy it.
(Sold 45 orders)
Enjoy.
One more order.
Three or four?
Four? She told me to order four.
Five?
She's saying 5. Should we get 5?
Okay.
Get all of them. Let's go all in.
Aunties Kitchen has sold 50 plates.
Okay. This is the last one.
- Are we done?
- Yes, we just finished.
Aunties Kitchen. Open the second box.
(3rd to sell out 50 orders)
How many more?
- Two more.
- Okay.
Enjoy.
Yes, it's yours. Enjoy.
(Sold 50 orders)
Kids Restaurant has sold 50 plates.
Yes, here's your cotton candy.
Enjoy. Thank you.
How many more containers? Why so many?
- We should make ten.
- Okay.
- We...
- Please hurry.
- We got too many penalties.
- We need to hurry.
If there were no penalties...
Let's serve.
Did we make it?
- Did we make it?
- Not yet.
Are we last?
(The octopus is on the verge of defeat.)
We can do it!
- We can do it!
- Yes, we can!
I should say cheering words.
After all, we're a team.
Keep it up. We've got eight more left.
- Eight?
- Yes.
- Okay, seven left.
- Okay.
Come on. Six left.
- Six.
- Yes.
- Here, cotton candies.
- We're almost done.
How many more cotton candies?
Two more.
- Here's your order.
- Two more.
(Sold 49 orders)
Who didn't get a cotton candy?
(Sold 50 orders)
Chef Land has sold 50 plates.
Okay!
Open the second box.
- Okay, our next box is open.
- Good.
If we fail...
Fail?
Is there no night opening?
To hang out before you leave?
- Yes, since we're here.
- Let's go together.
Isn't there a parade today?
- Really?
- Yes.
(At the amusement park,)
(a lively parade is in full swing.)
(An exciting parade by day)
(A multimedia show and fireworks by night)
(There's plenty to see and enjoy all day long.)
Parade or not, we will keep pumping out dishes.
Call it out.
The moment an order comes in, call it out.
As of now, the only restaurant...
still stuck on their first containers...
is Lulu Land.
(Lulu Land)
Darn it.
I was anxious,
and all thoughts raced through my head.
We were dropping to last place.
How could we fall from first all the way to last?
It felt like a roller coaster.
Peaking at the top, then entering free fall. It was us.
How were we going into the second half in last place?
(Go Seok Hyun)
(The padlock for the second half still remains unopened.)
Please make it quick.
- Okay.
- They're waiting out front.
Shrimp and...
Do you need shrimp now?
We're out of shrimp.
- Shrimp?
- Darn it.
Please let me know in advance when we're running low on something.
Just fry everything up. We're out of everything.
Okay.
Chef Sung Hoon's cooking style...
felt like a master craftsman,
so we couldn't really rush him.
(Frying time per portion)
(3 minutes)
(He'd have to fry non-stop for about 2 hours to pull this off.)
Just keep handing over the finished dishes.
Okay.
While frying the food, I could really feel it.
That the orders were backing up.
"Come on. Hurry up with the fried food."
Frying tendon in real time and serving it right away...
is not easy time-wise.
Did you get the call?
I have not received the call notification yet.
We are calling customers in order right now,
so it might take a while.
But it's been 30 minutes already.
We will have it ready shortly.
We will make it quick.
- We will get it done quickly.
- Please take it.
(The customers finally received the DonDon Set after a long wait.)
We're like food fighters now.
- Finally, it's Lulu Land.
- Finally.
- This is good.
- Yes.
(Humming)
(It is good enough to make up for the long wait.)
What kind of sauce is this?
(However)
The poached egg and fatsia shoots are missing.
This is unbelievable.
(Conger eel, shrimp, fatsia shoots, oyster mushroom,)
(squash, green chilli pepper, laver, poached egg)
We waited so long.
And they did not even give us the egg.
(Lulu Land)
Two plates are added to Lulu Land as a penalty.
Oh, no.
I think it is probably because there was a wait.
(The first penalty is incurred.)
(The udon is great, and the tendon tastes like one from a restaurant.)
(I like that the fried food is hot, but it takes way too long.)
(This is no ordinary tendon. I enjoyed the meal.)
(Despite positive reviews, there are many complaints about the wait.)
It's all right, Chef.
"Everyone is doing their best right now,"
"but how much time do we have left?"
I was feeling very anxious, but I didn't want to show it.
I didn't want to waver.
(Lee Sung Hoon and Go Seok Hyun)
Let us all focus on right here...
- until we sell all these dishes.
- Okay.
It's all right.
It's okay. We only need to take second place.
- Thank you.
Enjoy your food.
- Enjoy your food.
- Thank you. I'll enjoy the food.
We have only two left.
- Fry two servings?
- Yes.
- Then we're done?
Thank you.
(The last dish of the first half is served to the customer.)
Lulu Land has sold 50 plates.
(Clear time)
(Lee Yeon Bok and Kim Min Seong: 70 minutes)
(Lee Sung Hoon and Go Seok Hyun: 97 minutes)
Please open the second box.
I felt so rushed.
We finished the first half in last place.
So we were running out of time.
My hands were shaking as I unlocked the padlock.
(They start the 2nd half in last place after being in 1st.)
(About to smash the box)
(The 1st chef: Lee Sung Hoon)
(Sold out)
(The 2nd chef: Go Seok Hyun)
Please slice it now.
- I'll slice it.
- Okay.
The name of our menu item is full-topping futomaki.
Do you have any preferred container?
I personally like long ones like this.
Something simple.
(Go Seok Hyun chose the rectangular tray for the second half.)
I thought it should look cute.
So I made...
an animated character using a hole puncher.
(Adding cuteness to target children)
I made quail egg sunny-side-ups to put on top.
(Adding cute mini fried eggs)
(Planning to place it on top of the futomaki)
I thought there might be young kids too.
- It contains no raw ingredients.
- It's good.
- It usually has things like salmon.
- I see. No raw ingredients?
Parents would be reluctant to buy raw food for their kids.
So I made...
beef futomaki...
and egg futomaki.
I thought it would be made in big pieces,
but it was made rather delicate and pretty.
And I added delicious toppings on it.
The concept was for various flavours to burst in the mouth...
from the very first bite.
We need to catch up.
No orders have come in yet.
- I'll slice it first for now.
- Okay.
But no orders are coming in yet.
We didn't get any orders yet.
Should we try this?
- It has cucumber in it.
- Gosh.
No, it is already made.
Is it possible to get the futomaki without cucumber?
I do not think we can make it without cucumber.
- Okay.
- I am sorry.
- We can make it without cucumber.
- We will leave out cucumber.
We can do it without cucumber.
- We will make it right away.
- We can do that.
- Will you make one for us?
- Yes. We'll make it right away.
- Please place your order.
- Okay. Thank you.
It was so terrifying when the chefs stared at me.
(Laughing)
Now is not the time to be picky about orders.
- Make one without cucumber.
- Okay.
(Every single customer is precious.)
- This is the one without cucumber.
- Okay.
Please wait just one minute.
- Without cucumber?
- Yes.
This is the futomaki with no cucumber.
- Thank you. I'll enjoy it.
- It doesn't have cucumber in it.
Okay. Thank you.
Please enjoy it.
Let us just get some momentum going.
We have to catch up.
(Solemnly throwing off the apron)
(Putting on cuteness)
(Lulu is unsealed.)
- The hamster is coming out.
- Hamster?
The hamster is here.
It's the hamster!
Hi, hamster.
(Hello)
What's that?
(Gourmet toppings to put on top of futomaki)
"On top of the futomaki..."
(What will be the fate of Lee Sung Hoon and Go Seok Hyun?)
(Currently at the amusement park...)
(Kids Restaurant and Crazy Flavour Restaurant)
Did you get the ice cream ready?
- Shall we get ice cream now?
- I will scoop the ice cream now.
Okay.
(The first restaurant)
The second.
We're in second place.
(2nd place in the 1st half, Kim Kwan Hoon and Kim Ho Yoon)
We came up from last place to second place now.
I know.
(What is the second half menu of Kim Kwan Hoon and Kim Ho Yoon?)
(Dubai chewy bouncy mianbao xia)
Puppy, take orders for mianbao xia.
- DCB mianbao xia.
- Gosh, there's a puppy.
- Their menu changed to mianbao xia.
- Yes.
What is Dubai chewy bouncy mianbao xia?
Dubai chewy bouncy mianbao xia...
with real lemon yogurt gelato is only 13 dollars.
- It sounds good.
- Shall we try one?
For the second half, Crazy Flavour Restaurant prepared...
something that works as both a snack and a dessert.
We served DCB mianbao xia...
and lemon yogurt gelato in the rectangular tray.
We took inspiration from Dubai chewy cookies.
We used squid ink bread.
(Squid ink bread instead of cacao powder)
Instead of crispy kataifi,
we fried spring roll pastry in butter to put inside.
Then we added tapioca pearls to bring out the chewiness.
(Tapioca pearls, kataifi)
Bouncy shrimp balls.
(The filling has the characteristics of Dubai chewy cookies.)
Preserving all the crispiness, chewiness,
and bounciness.
The mianbao xia is easy to eat, yet packed with flavours.
(That's how the DCB mianbao xia is created.)
It is targeted at Gen Z.
What we intended came out quite well.
It looks delicious.
DCB mianbao xia?
I need to scoop the ice cream.
Since ice cream is preferred when the weather is hot,
we prepared freshly made lemon yogurt ice cream.
Customers need to see this texture.
(Handmade lemon yogurt gelato)
It's very chewy.
It is a menu item we are so confident in.
With the ice cream, they can settle dessert at once.
- This is freshly made.
- Thank you.
Thank you. It will be delicious.
(Crazy Flavour Restaurant has sold 59 plates.)
(DCB mianbao xia and lemon yogurt gelato)
- Is it good?
- Yes.
The bread is crispy, yet it melts in your mouth.
- There is so much shrimp.
- I know.
The bread is really crispy,
but it does not taste oily at all.
It would be perfect if we only had beer.
It'd be perfect with beer.
(Despite the positive reviews, the booth is quiet.)
Please enjoy it.
(Sighing)
Did the customers suddenly stop coming?
Compared to the number of customers there,
I thought our ordering speed was not very fast.
(Unlike the hectic first half,)
(the second half is quiet.)
This is DCB mianbao xia.
You know I hate Dubai chewy cookies.
Dubai chewy bouncy mianbao xia?
It says Dubai chewy bouncy mianbao xia.
- Okay.
- Do you want to try this?
- No.
- You don't want it?
It's called "Dubai chewy."
I am starting to feel a bit repelled by it.
There are way too many similar products.
(Dubai chewy is a love-it-or-hate-it item.)
The menu item named "Dubai chewy" might have made it...
difficult to build sympathy with customers.
(Dubai chewy bouncy mianbao xia)
How are the other places doing? Is there a long line?
(The line for Kids Restaurant)
That line is not for us.
I don't know if it was because we were Crazy Flavour Restaurant,
but all I could see were children.
I felt so anxious having Kids Restaurant right next door.
They just do not match.
Crazy Flavour Restaurant and Kids Restaurant don't go well.
It would be weird for both of them to survive together.
We were targeting Gen Z.
I thought that one of us was not going to work out.
That's how I felt.
(What's the second half menu of Choi Sang Hyun and Kim Hoon?)
(Please take a look at this!)
(Ice cream churros and lasagna cheese balls)
(Kim Hoon chose the soda pop container for the second half.)
For the second half,
we prepared ice cream churros and lasagna cheese balls.
(The 1st chef: Choi Sang Hyun)
(Sold out)
(The 2nd chef: Kim Hoon)
We sold a pasta menu in the first half,
and for the second half,
we prepared a dessert with churros, ice cream, and cheese balls.
It's for kids, and it's what I'm most confident in.
(A dessert menu targeting children)
It is a menu item I have sold for a long time at my restaurant.
I have my own data showing that whenever I make lasagna,
I win.
Whenever I make lasagna, I win.
That's why we prepared lasagna.
Since the concept was set as the Kids Restaurant for kids,
I thought about what mothers could easily feed their children.
So I made the lasagna into bite-sized pieces for easy eating.
After boiling conchiglie pasta,
you stuff it with a filling made of ragu and cheese mixed together...
and shape it like dumplings.
It feels like a major holiday.
Is it Chuseok or something?
- Please fry that up quickly for me.
- Okay.
(Pre-frying it so the food can go out fast)
And what is the menu item people eat the most at an amusement park?
It is churros.
So I added churros.
Lasagna and churros.
Plus ice cream that can be eaten together on a hot day.
That is the ultimate three-step combo.
I put those three together as the ultimate weapon.
If I pull out this card, I will definitely win.
I'll win this time.
(Ice cream churros and lasagna cheese balls)
(Same dessert category, different target audience)
(Eagerly promoting in front of another booth)
(Please try the lasagna.)
(You get free cotton candy.)
It's holding up a signboard.
It looks like they will fight.
(Children are approaching, captivated by the cotton candy.)
Cotton candy.
- Cotton candy.
- Cotton candy!
Come. You should take it.
How will you get it? Do you want to try this?
(Nodding)
(Ordering)
I don't like lemon ice cream.
This isn't lemon ice cream.
This one?
(Ordering)
Hi, Teddy Bear!
(Explosive interest from children)
(A bite of churros dipped in ice cream)
- This is really good.
- I want a bite!
- It's not a cheese stick. Try it.
- Help yourself.
This is really...
This is a lot better.
- The lasagna tastes good.
- It's delicious, right?
It's very crispy and tasty.
Currently, Kids Restaurant...
has sold 75 plates.
- Nice.
We finished half.
The kid-friendly concept is working out well today.
It's all about children.
Not even middle schoolers, just kids.
If they had been teenagers, we would have won.
Giving out free cotton candy made a huge difference.
No, high schoolers would not go there.
Puppy, walk around carrying the ice cream.
- Ice cream.
- No, there's no need.
Just write...
"handmade gelato ice cream" on the whiteboard.
No, I'll write it.
I have pretty handwriting.
People are looking for ice cream,
but if you say gelato, they do not recognise it.
You have to call it gelato ice cream.
As I observed the place dressed as a puppy,
I found out that the customers were already full.
I'm full.
- Are you full?
- Yes.
Is there any room left in your stomach?
- Not really, but I want to eat.
- Are you full?
So there were a lot of people looking only for desserts.
(The customers are looking for desserts, feeling full.)
There's ice cream.
- Ice cream!
- It's ice cream.
(Responding to Kim Hoon's signboard)
- Is that gelato?
- Where?
How about ice cream churros?
(We have gelato over there!)
Since I could not speak, I tried to observe people a lot.
I thought there would be a high preference for gelato.
(Handmade gelato ice cream)
(Crazy Flavour Restaurant)
(Promoting primarily with ice cream)
I want to eat this at a restaurant, not at an amusement park.
- Are you hungry?
- Hello.
- Are you alone?
- Handmade gelato ice cream?
(Hiding)
Which restaurant are you from?
Where?
- Over there?
- Crazy flavour Restaurant?
Lemon yogurt gelato?
- Okay.
I want to try the gelato.
- Me too.
- For dessert.
(Focusing on the customers who are having a meal)
But yogurt gelato is a dessert.
- There is always room for dessert.
- I can eat more.
I can't eat anymore.
You should open up the stomach for dessert.
You can eat dessert.
This is driving me crazy.
(Order)
Now the orders are coming in.
They say it is super fresh gelato made today.
I want to eat gelato.
Ice cream!
(Kwan Hoon's efforts successfully attract customers.)
We just need to match the speed.
It will be ready shortly.
We have to catch up.
Please get me one ice cream.
Okay.
This is freshly made lemon yogurt ice cream.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Gelato?
(Puppy is sneaking over.)
Puppy!
(Wandering Panda's ice cream, Kids Restaurant's ice cream)
I asked you to do a high-five, but why aren't you doing it?
The gelato?
High-five!
(Puppy is upset.)
After seeing it work so hard, we should buy the mianbao xia.
We should do that.
(They ended up buying Crazy Flavour Restaurant's dish.)
Even though we have three different ice cream options.
(Trying the lemon gelato)
- This is really good.
- Is it?
It's so delicious.
(Comparing and analysing the 3 ice cream shops)
- This is different.
- Right.
This one is the most delicious among all three ice creams.
I know, right?
(Among the ice creams of the three shops,)
(Crazy Flavour Restaurant takes 1st place.)
I would have regretted it if I had not tried this.
The gelato is the most delicious.
- Let's go.
- Let's go. Let's speed up.
Hang in there, Puppy.
I became a mad dog.
I worked so hard. I think I did really well.
I felt so proud of myself.
Nice, just a little bit more.
I'd be upset if we lost.
(Crazy Flavour Restaurant has sold 73 plates.)
Is the booth next door serving just soft ice cream?
- Yes, it is.
- Yes.
- If that's the case...
- They can't...
dispense 50 servings continuously.
It's impossible.
Did you get the ice cream ready, Jong In?
- Not yet.
- Not a single one?
- No.
- Can you do it for a second?
About the ice cream... The machine...
dispenses 5 servings...
and needs to rest for 15 minutes to get another 5.
It's an emergency. The ice cream is melting right now.
Even when dispensed immediately, it melts right away.
It seems like it can only do up to ten servings at a time.
- Really?
- We only need to dispense 50.
Right.
We have to get them all done during the first half.
How many do we have now?
I will head back out again.
I put on the bear mascot head and took it off to get ice cream.
So we had some that was done during the first half.
(Frowning)
Is there enough ice cream? Do we need more?
Just get some more if you have spare time.
We have about 20 servings. Get some more.
Okay.
It's so hot.
Hang in there, Teddy Bear.
Hoon, go and attract customers.
- Do what?
- What?
Drink some water.
I'll put it in here. I think we have enough.
Honestly, I was seeing stars.
I thought I was getting heatstroke.
This is killing me.
(Amid the fierce dessert war)
Okay. Once these go out, we are set.
We are switching to the second container right away.
We have to get rid of all these.
- I'll take them outside.
- Take them outside.
Chef, I will put the sauces and these items outside.
Clear everything out. We don't need any of it.
- I will bring the soda as well.
- Okay.
(Switching to the second half)
(Second half: Edward Kwon)
(Edward Kwon chose the rectangular tray.)
Before this mission,
I went to Lotte World once and Everland twice.
Today, I'm at the amusement park in Yongin...
where the third mission will take place.
I noticed...
there were many food choices available.
So I thought...
it'd be a good idea...
to help people try a bit of everything.
So it contains the most dishes so far.
It's the global lunch box...
with orange cream shrimp and chicken steak.
(Global lunch box)
(Shrimp, chicken)
For the orange cream shrimp...
It's called the orange zest. It's ground orange skin.
We're using the orange to give the flavour.
(Fresh cream sauce on fried shrimp)
And chicken steak using the peanut glaze.
I was thinking about Thai-style food.
Then I decided to use the peanut butter.
Amazing.
The chicken looks just perfect.
(Roasted chicken steak)
(With the Thai-style peanut glaze sauce)
(Exclaiming)
This is good.
I love the scent of peanut.
And a lot of visitors pack lunch...
to Everland.
So I decided to include fried tofu rice balls.
(Japanese)
Then I saw nachos and tacos.
(Cheese quesadilla, Mexican)
I decided to add salad...
to keep the balance and refresh the palate.
(Tomato pasta salad, western)
If I include them all in one box,
the customers don't have to worry...
about what to eat.
So it's guaranteed to thrive.
How is that available only for 13 dollars?
- It's impossible.
- You can't find it anywhere else.
Wait.
We need to put up the poster.
That's right.
(The first menu's still up for Aunties Kitchen.)
- Chef, do you want me to go?
- Will you do that for me?
Take it off and come back right away.
Okay. Got it.
Chef.
I can't fit in this uniform.
I should do it.
- Okay. Leave the shrimp and go.
- Okay.
- I'll go. Okay.
- He's the fastest.
- Okay.
- He's so excited.
I'm good at it.
Chef, here. I'll pass it to you in front.
Okay.
(Aunties Kitchen)
(Promoting the restaurant while he's out)
Aunties Kitchen switched to chicken steak.
Where?
- The menu changed.
- Would you like to place the order?
We're getting orders.
- It's coming in.
- Four.
- Four each.
Yes, four each.
(After placing 5 different kinds of dishes)
I just need the shrimp to be prepared.
They're ready to be served.
- Give plenty.
- Okay.
- Is this enough?
- Yes.
(Plenty of handmade sauce)
Here you are. Enjoy.
(Aunties Kitchen, 51 servings sold)
- I think this is the best for you.
- Yes.
It also comes with this...
We can try both.
(People showing interest in the diverse composition of the menu)
(Orders pour in.)
- We need four.
- Okay.
- Six orders.
Enjoy.
Next.
Thank you. Enjoy.
We're getting more.
We're getting more. Let's hurry up.
Every time that rings, I feel like getting a breakdown.
(Current time: 2:19pm)
We have a street restaurant...
that sold all servings.
We have first place.
I'm jealous.
(Lee Sung Hoon and Go Seok Hyun of Lulu Land?)
We're getting orders.
- Oh, no.
- I got it.
- Let's get it over with soon.
- Okay.
Keep it up. Focus.
- How many? Three?
- Three each.
(Kim Mi Ryeong and Edward Kwon of Aunties Kitchen?)
We can't be 2nd. We must place 1st.
We can do it.
(Out of six teams,)
(which team will be the first to survive?)
The sold-out restaurant.
(The sold-out restaurant...)
Kids Restaurant survives.
(Kids Restaurant places 1st...)
(in the 100 serving relay team match.)
That was fast.
(Exclaiming)
They placed first.
That's crazy. I knew he was good.
Oh, that place... Kids Restaurant is good.
(After placing 4th in the 1st half,)
(the line never ended.)
(Sold out 50 minutes after the second half began)
- Good job.
- Thank you.
- You're awesome.
- Good job.
- We did it.
- I'm so proud of you all.
- Good job.
- For the second half,
we focused...
on a fulfilling dessert.
We prepared ice cream, fried lasagna,
and churros.
We made a strategic approach.
Look. Ice cream churros and lasagna cheese balls.
Do you want this? They also give us free cotton candy.
We expected over 90 percent of visitors...
to be families with children under school age.
Free cotton candy.
Is that why you chose this place?
(Laughing)
You chose it for the cotton candy.
How's the ice cream, Byeong Woo?
Five points.
I think somebody very smart came up with it.
They knew children were coming.
(Every table with children has...)
(ice cream, churros, and lasagna cheese balls.)
We're serving faster than other teams.
We're the top.
(Speeding up the turnover by cooking in advance)
- I'm taking it.
- We're almost there.
One person was frying. Seung Jae was plating.
We were able to serve very fast.
Thank you. Enjoy.
(Kids Restaurant, 98 servings sold)
Thank you.
Enjoy.
- Enjoy.
(Kids Restaurant had a perfect strategy.)
All thanks to you, Seung Jae, and Jong In.
You're soaked in sweat.
It was perfect.
Good job.
You did a great job in the hot weather.
He almost had heatstroke.
We placed first.
(Smiling)
Oh, ice cream.
The dessert is unbeatable.
It's neck and neck.
The difference is only a few.
Only a few differences...
decide 1st and 2nd places.
Right now, Wandering Panda is...
in the bottom place.
(Wandering Panda by Lee Yeon Bok and Kim Min Seong is at the bottom.)
(Kids Restaurant by Choi Sang Hyun and Kim Hoon survived.)
- What was their name again?
- Wandering Panda?
There must be a problem.
- At first...
- Weren't they in the lead at first?
They were in the lead at first.
- They were in the lead.
- That's what I mean.
(Bottom place, Wandering Panda)
What do we do?
We got a few at first, but we're not getting any more.
There are no customers.
(There are no customers on our side.)
(No customers for Wandering Panda)
How come we're not getting any customers?
What's the matter?
I was kind of flustered.
At first, the orders came in.
Then eventually, it stopped.
(Despite Yeon Bok Panda's touting...)
(Passing)
(Looking away)
(Customers pass him.)
(People saw the menu, but they pass.)
(Shaking his head)
We should be serving.
We're the only ones with no customers.
- Everyone else has a line.
- Really?
Why is that? The ice cream...
Honestly,
I was worried about the latter team.
After that, people can have it for dessert.
This will be a meal replacement.
- With ham and vegetables?
- Yes, vegetables.
- But...
- With vegetables and stuff.
those two look kind of expensive...
for a 13 dollar dish.
- It's not exactly...
- So I think...
- appealing...
- ham...
- Exactly.
- People need to see it.
Other places have a strong second menu.
Other places have a strong menu?
They have something like lemon yogurt ice cream...
There are three ice cream places.
(In the Street Arena,)
(Kids Restaurant, Wandering Panda, Crazy Flavour Restaurant)
(there are 3 dessert places.)
(Kim Hoon, Kim Min Seong, Kim Ho Yoon)
(Kim Min Seong lost the ice cream battle.)
Ice cream churros and lasagna cheese balls?
Do you want to try the yogurt gelato?
When you order it, you get churros and ice cream together.
It's freshly made handmade ice cream.
Do you want to try the churros?
- It's very good. Try one.
- Try one.
It's even better if you dip it in the ice cream.
It tastes like yogurt...
(Exclaiming)
It tastes like real lemon yogurt gelato.
(Compared to the two popular restaurants...)
It looks like ordinary vanilla ice cream.
It's not handmade.
- Whereas this is handmade.
- Right.
It's nothing special.
We need something special.
(Wandering Panda's ice cream is rather ordinary.)
I wouldn't get a sandwich.
They're separate.
It's a combo.
You can't just have ice cream. It comes with a sandwich.
Oh, it's a combo.
Do you want this or...
We'll come back.
(People turn around.)
"Is this that lame?"
That thought frustrated me.
There's no point in promoting.
You'll get sick. You can stop.
(Although he did his best to draw customers,)
(there are still many trays left for the second half.)
(They look outside with worries.)
(Empty)
(Restless)
Who's next to us? Hong Seok Cheon?
- Yes.
- Their line is endless.
The menu...
(Chef Land has many customers.)
Should we change the menu?
What do we have? We don't even have ketchup.
(Yeon Bok plans to change the menu.)
(They look for ingredients in a rush.)
What time are we open till?
Probably around 3pm.
It won't go past 3pm.
So it's already too late...
to change the menu.
(It's open from noon to 3pm in the amusement park.)
I felt bad.
This is bad. Did we choose the wrong menu?
- Chef Land. Go, go, go!
- Go, go, go!
- Let's go!
- Yes.
How many? Ten?
Actually, when I was cooking,
I was expecting to place first.
(Lee Yeon Bok placed 1st in the 1st half.)
Then from first place, we were about to place bottom.
I went from one extreme to another.
Wandering Panda is...
fifteen servings away from the lead.
(Wandering Panda is 15 servings away from the lead.)
I feel bad for Chef Lee Yeon Bok.
I feel so bad for him.
(Glancing)
Gosh.
I feel so bad for causing you trouble.
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, no.
What can we do?
No one saw this coming.
I realised...
how tough a team match is.
Because I can't control it.
(Only one spot remains.)
(Penalty servings are added.)
(Unless they figure out the reason,)
(they'll get more penalties.)
(Hey. Do it right.)
(Why can't he trust me?)
(Teamwork falls apart even more.)
(But they must stop their restaurants from closing.)
(They make the final push.)
- Last three left.
- Three more to go.
(One more to go.)
(Fierce battle over one last spot)
(Who's going to survive among them?)
(Round 4 semifinal)
(I was very nervous.)
("Where on earth am I?")
("Are we going to start as soon as we get off?")
(I'm kind of scared.)
(Where on earth are we going?)
(We're here.)
(This is tense.)
The mission will take place in...
(Incheon International Airport)
(The biggest gate before going global)
(The place where an exciting journey begins)
(Who will win the last ticket to the final?)